<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on IT-Premium the premium support for IT services</title>
    <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on IT-Premium the premium support for IT services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workplace and Standard Software Support Service: Overview</title>
      <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/it-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/it-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The workplace and standard software (SW) support service ensures the stable operation of operating systems and office applications. We provide professional assistance in troubleshooting, installing, and reinstalling software. Discover how our support benefits businesses and individual users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;which-software-do-we-support&#34;&gt;Which Software Do We Support?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our team handles the following versions of standard software:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows Operating Systems:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Server&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Office Suite:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Office&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Office 365&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These versions remain popular among users, and we guarantee their seamless performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need to Know About IT Audit: How to Optimize Your IT Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/audit-and-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/audit-and-consulting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced technological world, businesses must stay competitive. One key tool to achieve this is an &lt;strong&gt;IT audit&lt;/strong&gt;. This service evaluates your information infrastructure, identifies weaknesses, and offers ways to improve it. In this article, we’ll explain what an IT audit is, why it’s essential, and how it can benefit your company.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-an-it-audit&#34;&gt;What is an IT Audit?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An &lt;strong&gt;IT audit&lt;/strong&gt; is a comprehensive review of a company’s information systems, including hardware, software, network infrastructure, data security, and compliance with standards. The goal is to assess the efficiency of IT processes, identify risks, and provide recommendations for improvement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAS Platform Support: Professional Business Assistance</title>
      <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/remote-server-bas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/remote-server-bas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We provide professional support services for the BAS (former 1C) Platform, ensuring stable operation of your information system.&lt;/strong&gt; Our experts are ready to promptly respond to technical incidents and provide real-time quality support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Levels and Response Times&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To meet various business needs, we offer three service levels:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platinum Support Level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Response time: 30 minutes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolution time: up to 8 hours&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maximum priority ticket processing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gold Support Level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Response time: 1 hour&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolution time: up to 12 hours&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced priority ticket processing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Classic Support Level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Security and Backup: A Key IT Service in Outsourcing for Your Business</title>
      <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/backup-and-restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/backup-and-restore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital world, where data is the foundation of any business, ensuring its security and reliable backup is not just an option—it’s a necessity. IT outsourcing offers a comprehensive service, &amp;ldquo;Data Security and Backup,&amp;rdquo; enabling companies to protect their information from cyber threats, hardware failures, and other risks. In this article, we’ll explore why this service is critically important, how it operates within IT outsourcing, and the benefits it brings to businesses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Networks: Building, Maintenance, and IT Infrastructure Setup</title>
      <link>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://it-premium.com.ua/en/services/networks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Local networks (LANs) form the backbone of modern IT infrastructure for businesses, offices, and even home users. They enable fast data exchange, stable internet access, and seamless interaction between devices. In this article, we’ll explore the key aspects of building and maintaining local networks, selecting server equipment, configuring routers, and diagnosing incidents to ensure your network runs smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-is-a-local-network-and-why-does-it-matter&#34;&gt;What is a Local Network and Why Does It Matter?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A local network is a system that connects computers, servers, printers, and other devices within a single space, such as an office or home. It facilitates rapid data transfer, centralized resource management, and reliable internet access. A well-designed local network boosts productivity, reduces IT maintenance costs, and ensures consistent performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
